{
    "subject": "resource/The_Movielife",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "The Movielife is from United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9805155992507935,
            "question": "Is The Movielife a film from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9455057978630066,
            "question": "Is The Movielife American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9023854732513428,
            "question": "Is The Movielife American-made?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7348738312721252,
            "question": "Can we assume The Movielife is a US production?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6412827968597412,
            "question": "Where is The Movielife from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48331788182258606,
            "question": "What is The Movielife's origin country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47520318627357483,
            "question": "What country is The Movielife associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45011425018310547,
            "question": "What nationality is The Movielife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41390854120254517,
            "question": "Where was The Movielife produced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40645939111709595,
            "question": "To which country does The Movielife belong?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Movielife is from United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9057_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was The Movielife produced?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9057_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality is The Movielife?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9057_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is The Movielife associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9057_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9057_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9057_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9057_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9057_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9057_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9057_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9057_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9057_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9057_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9057_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information clearly states that The Movielife hails from New York, which is in the United States. Therefore, the statement \"The Movielife is from the United States\" is supported by the given documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The text states they hail from New York.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}